13.4%
of all skills published have at least
one critical security vulnerability.
What can we as users of these skills do
to protect ourselves and block
potentially malicious skills from our
development environments?
>> I think the models are getting better
and better and they will will [music]
produce better code. If you look at what
the training data for that is, there are
still a lot of vulnerabilities in there.
Yeah,
>> may not be massive vulnerabilities, but
even smaller vulnerabilities if you
chain them together can end up in an
attack chain and therefore be massively
destructive.
>> We now have an integration between Sneak
and Tessle, which is all about adding
sneak security scans into [music] the
Tesla registry. Tell us a little bit
about the sneak agent scan that scans
MCPs and skills.
>> You can see MCPS as as the the next
supply chain problem, right? you are
adding features and functions to your
LLM or to your to your uh agent in this
case. [music] Um so it can execute that
but what kind of stuff is there? If you
trust it now it's good but what will the
followup what will the new version do?
But we also scan skills. And because
it's just plain text, they can be
vulnerable to all sorts of [music]
things like prompt injections with B64
encoding. And there are all sorts of
things that you don't want to blindly
have in a skill. But since a skill file
can be quite big, you don't want to do
that manually.
>> And on every skill that's in the Tesla
registry, a sneak scan has occurred and
[music] the results of those sneak scan
is right there by the by the skill. And
you can click on that and you can find
more information about what the
criticality uh of the outcome if there
if there are issues. and also you know
click in for more information actually
identify what does this actually mean
and what can I do about it
>> if you use the tel tesle registry then
or you already informed [music] that
what kind of problems are there so not
just blindly install them look at what
is the intention of the skill how are
you going to use them what kind of
privileges do you give to that project
if I can say it like that um that the
skill has access to and then make
[music] your informed decision
>> go to tesleio/registry
check out the skills that exist on the
registry and and take a look at the
sneak scans that uh that show potential
vulnerable issues that exist within
[music] those skills today. Thanks very
much, Brian, and thanks for tuning in.